Muhammad Dzaki Izza Romadhon

Jakarta 12630 | https:// https://www.linkedin.com/in/dzaki-izza | 081210901616 | dzakiizza02@gmail.com Portfolio: https://dzakiizza-portfolio-app.vercel.app

SUMMARY

Highly passionate and interest in technology. Experienced in software development process from the concept or problem statement through development and deliver the end product as solution. Capable to work effectively with a different roles and team in dynamic environment. An eager learner who dedicated to improve and maintain tools, also learn new things to maximise productivity so that could get a better result or performance of product.

WORK EXPERIENCES

Software Engineer (Contract Employee)

(April 2024 – Present)

PT Perusahaan Gas Negara (PGN)

- Responsible to handle modules / feature development of web based application using .NET Framework.
- Designed and maintained the database relation including tables, function and store procedure using SQL Server.
- Working closely with the user to ensure the result is as what expected.

Frontend Engineer (Full Time Employee)

(September 2022 – November 2023)

PT Feedloop Global Teknologi

- Developed a frontend of AI based application and make sure the experience matches the product design using Next JS.
- Enhanced and maintained a frontend low-code software development platform on application builder using React JS.
- Created a well formatted modular code, perform testing and debugging of application.

UI/UX Designer (Internship)

(February 2021 – December 2021)

Apple Developer Academy @BINUS

- Gathered business requirements and problem statements through qualitative and quantitative R&D such as interviews, desk research, and surveys to improve the product quality.
- Designed application interfaces start from wireframe, low to high fidelity prototype design based on Human Interface Guidelines and UI style guide for iOS app using Figma App.
- Practiced and implemented multiple development processes including Scrum, Agile, Design Thinking, and business application analysis to ensure the solution concepts are positioned around the customer values and needs

PROJECTS

UPGRDE (https://upgrade.pgn.co.id)

A web application to manage & generate pricing for operation maintenance division in Perusahaan Gas Negara (Internal Usage)

Feedloop AI (https://platform.feedloop.ai)

A web application that helps to craft and manage tailored AI Co-Pilots, uniquely designed to streamline a specific business process.

Buatin App (https://buatin.app)

A standalone web application that's act as landing page to help you build an application using low code platform.

• Anime App (https://anime-app-nu.vercel.app)

A web application to showing list of anime and maintain a collection of preferred anime.

EDUCATION

Bina Nusantara University – Jakarta, Indonesia

(September 2018 – February 2022)

Bachelor of Information Systems - Major in Business Intelligence

GPA 3.68 / 4.00

SKILLS

Technical Skills: Web Development (React JS, Next JS, Node JS, Typescript, Javascript, C#, .NET, CSS & HTML), React Native, RESTful API, SQL Server & PostgreSQL, SEO, UI/UX Design (Figma, Sketch & Canva), Git.

Soft Skills: Communication (Effectively & Confidently), Collaboration, Problem Solver, Attention to Detail, Adaptability, Teamwork, Leadership, Analysis, Growth Mindset, Critical Thinking, Innovative & Creative.